UNESCO Second Canadian Archaeological Expedition to Carthage Records MS210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Excavation site images, 1905 -- 2002; MS210.004; 7.45 Linear Feet; 1424 Digital Object(s)
  - 2CC78, 1978 -- 1979; MS210.004.004
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00003 (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00003.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00003.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004 (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00004.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005 (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 5KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00005.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006 (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 6KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00006.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007 (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00007.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008 (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 7KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00008.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009 (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00009.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010 (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 8KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00010.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011 (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 9KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00011.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012 (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00012.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013 (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 10KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00013.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014 (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 11KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00014.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015 (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00015.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016 (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 12KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00016.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017 (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00017.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018 (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 13KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00011; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00012; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00013; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00014; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00015; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00016; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00017; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00018; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00019; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00018.00020; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
    - 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019 (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00001; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00002; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00003; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00004; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00005; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00006; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00007; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00008; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00009; Wells, Colin (Box 2)
      - 14KR 2CC78, 1978; MS210.004.002.00019.00010; Wells, Colin (Box 2)